Wauregan and Quinebaug Company Records 1981.0010
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series XV: Administrative Records, 1853-1967
  - Subseries B: Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1938-1942
    - Correspondence, 1941 November - December (Box 369:5433)
    - Correspondence, 1942 January - April (Box 370:5434)
    - Correspondence, 1942 May - December (Box 370:5435)
    - Correspondence: "Confidential", 1938 (Box 370:5436)
    - Resolutions, 1939-1940 (Box 370:5437)
    - Resolutions, 1941-1942 (Box 370:5438)
    - Working papers, 1938-1941 (Box 370:5439)
    - Land records, 1936-1938 (Box 370:5440)
    - Land records, 1939 (Box 370:5441-5442)
    - Land records, 1940 (Box 370:5443)
    - Land records, 1941 (Box 370:5444)
    - Contracts, 1941 (Box 370:5445)
    - Contracts, undated (Box 370:5446)
    - Loans, 1939-1942 (Box 370:5447)
    - Loans, 1938-1940 (Box 370:5448)
    - Loans, 1939-1940 (Box 370:5449)
    - Profit/Loss statements, 1938 (Box 370:5450)
    - Inventories, 1938 (Box 371)
  - Subseries C: Legal Records, 1853-1967
    - Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1932-1943 (Box 446)
    - Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1935-1961 (Box 447)
    - Correspondence, 1933-1942 (Box 370:5451)
    - Contracts, 1933-1939 (Box 370:5452)
    - Contracts, 1940-1942 (Box 370:5453)
    - Deeds, 1943 (Box 424:5896)
    - Documents, 1853, 1899, 1932, 1949, 1954, 1957-1960, 1967 (Box 424:5895)
    - Land records, 1933-1939 (Box 370:5454)
    - Land records, 1940 (Box 370:5455)
    - Land records, 1941 (Box 370:5456-5457)
    - Land records, 1942 (Box 370:5458)
    - Patents, 1934, 1940-1941 (Box 370:5459)
  - Subseries D: Stock Records, 1932-1943
    - General, 1932-1943 (Box 370:5460)
    - Reorganization, 1932 (Box 370:5461-5462)
    - Reorganization (printed materials), 1932 (Box 372:5463)
    - Reorganiztion, 1942-1943 (Box 372:5464-5465)
    - Reorganization (printed materials), 1942 (Box 372:5466)
    - Reorganization--Dissenting stockholders, 1943 (Box 372:5467)
    - Proxy votes, 1933, 1935 (Box 372:5468)
    - Certificates, 1933 (Box 372:5469)
    - Dividend reports, 1942 (Box 372:5470)
  - Subseries E: Insurance Records, 1933-1948
    - General, 1933-1937 (Box 372:5471)
    - General, 1938-1941 (Box 372:5472)
    - General, 1942-1943 (Box 372:5473)
    - Appraisals, 1933 (Box 372:5474)
    - Appraisals, 1934 (Box 372:5475)
    - Appraisals, 1935 (Box 372:5476)
    - Policy accounts, 1934-1948 (Box 372:5477)
  - Subseries F: J. A. Atwood, III, 1949-1957
    - Wauregan Mills, Inc., 1949-1950 (Box 372:5478)
    - J. A. Atwood, 1956-1957 (Box 372:5479)
- Series XVI: General Accounts Records, 1929-1959
  - Account book, 1933-1934 (Box 373)
  - Account book, 1934-1935 (Box 374)
  - General journal, 1937-1942 (Box 375)
  - General journal, 1939-1941 (Box 376)
  - Journal A, 1932-1934 (Box 377)
  - Journal B, 1935-1938 (Box 378)
  - Journal C, 1938-1942 (Box 379)
  - Sales invoice register, 1941-1948 (Box 380)
  - Cash books, 1932-1936 (Box 381)
  - Cash books, 1936-1943 (Box 382)
  - Ledger, 1930-1932 (Box 387)
  - Ledger, 1932-1939 (Box 383)
  - Ledger, 1934-1935 (Box 386)
  - Ledger, 1937-1942 (Box 384)
  - Ledger, 1957-1959 (Box 385)
  - "Make up" Ledger, 1933-1939 (Box 388)
  - Balance sheets, 1929-1933 (Box 372:5480)
  - Balance sheets, 1934 (Box 372:5481)
  - Balance sheets, 1935 (Box 372:5482)
  - Balance sheets, 1936 (Box 372:5483)
  - Balance sheets, 1937 January - April (Box 372:5484)
  - Balance sheets, 1937 May - December (Box 372:5485)
  - Balance sheets, 1938 January (Box 372:5486)
  - Balance sheets, 1938 February - April (Box 372:5487)
  - Balance sheets, 1938 June - December (Box 372:5488)
  - Balance sheets, 1938 October (Box 372:5489)
  - Balance sheets, 1938 December (Box 372:5490-5491)
  - Balance sheets, 1939 January (Box 372:5492)
  - Balance sheets, 1939 March - April (Box 389:5493)
  - Balance sheets, 1939 April (Box 389:5494)
  - Balance sheets, 1939 May - December (Box 389:5495)
  - Balance sheets, 1942 (Box 389:5496)
  - Audits, 1940 (Box 389:5497)
  - Audits, 1941 (Box 389:5498)
  - Taxes, 1936 (Box 389:5499)
  - Taxes, 1937 (Box 389:5500-5501)
  - Taxes, 1938 (Box 389:5502)
  - Taxes, 1939 (Box 389:5503)
  - Taxes, 1940 (Box 389:5504-5505)
  - Taxes, 1941-1943 (Box 389:5506)
  - Trial balances, 1932-1937 (Box 390)
  - Trial balances, 1938-1941 (Box 391)
  - Trial balances, 1942-1943 (Box 392)
  - Pro-Forma Balance Sheet, 1932 (Box 441)
- Series XVII: Purchasing and Receiving Records, 1932-1943
  - Cotton reports, 1932 (Box 389:5507)
  - Cotton reports, 1932 (Box 393)
  - Cotton reports, 1932-1933 (Box 395)
  - Cotton reports, 1933 (Box 389:5508-5509)
  - Cotton reports, 1933-1934 (Box 394)
  - Cotton reports, 1934-1935 (Box 389:5510)
  - Cotton reports, 1934-1936 (Box 397)
  - Cotton reports, 1934-1940 (Box 396)
  - Cotton reports, 1936 (Box 389:5511)
  - Cotton reports, 1937 (Box 389:5512)
  - Cotton reports, 1937-1940 (Box 398)
  - Cotton reports, 1938 (Box 389:5513)
  - Inventory ledger, 1933 (Box 401)
  - Inventory ledger, 1933-1937 (Box 400)
  - Inventory ledger, 1933-1936 (Box 403)
  - Inventory ledger, 1934-1936 (Box 402)
  - Inventory ledger, 1937-1938 (Box 399)
  - Inventories, 1939 April (Box 389:5514)
  - Inventories, 1939 October (Box 389:5515)
  - Inventories, 1940 January - April (Box 389:5516)
  - Inventories, 1940 May - december (Box 389:5517)
  - Inventories, 1942 (Box 389:5518)
  - Finished goods, 1938-1939 (Box 389:5519)
  - Finished goods, 1940-1941 (Box 389:5520)
  - Invoice register, 1938-1943 (Box 405)
  - Invoice register, 1942 (Box 404)
- Series XVIII: Production, undated, 1932-1956
  - Weaving and spinning reports, undated (Box 406)
  - Cost of production, 1933 (Box 389:5521)
  - Cost of production, 1935 (Box 389:5522)
  - Cost of production, 1936 (Box 389:5523)
  - Cost of production, 1937 (Box 389:5524)
  - Cost of production, 1941 (Box 389:5525-5526)
  - Tyson Shirt Defect Analysis, 1955 July 11 (Box 407:5527)
  - Engineering studies
    - 1938 April - May (Box 407:5528)
    - 1938 June (Box 407:5529)
    - 1938 July (Box 407:5530-5531)
    - 1938 August - September (Box 407:5532)
    - 1938 October (Box 407:5533-5535)
    - 1939 (Box 407:5536)
    - 1941 (Box 407:5537)
  - Equipment records
    - Quinebaug, 1932 (Box 407:5538)
    - Wauregan, 1932 (Box 407:5539)
    - 1934 (Box 407:5540)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 407:5541)
    - 1942 (Box 407:5542)
    - Barber-Colman Spooler, 1947-1948 (Box 407:5543)
    - Card room, 1942-1948 (Box 407:5544)
    - Card room--Speeds, 1947 (Box 407:5545)
    - Cards, 1944-1948 (Box 407:5546)
    - Cards--Cotton, 1945-1948 (Box 407:5547)
    - Cards--Percentage Waste, 1947 (Box 407:5548)
    - Combers, 1944-1945 (Box 407:5549)
    - Doffer Study, 1947-1948 (Box 407:5550)
    - Lap Winder and Drawing frames, 1943-1948 (Box 407:5551)
    - Loom speeds, 1942-1948 (Box 407:5552)
    - Loom speeds, 1949-1951 (Box 407:5553)
    - Loom test--C & K, 1947-1948 (Box 407:5554)
    - Loom test--Plain drapers, 1946-1948 (Box 407:5555)
    - Loom test--Staffords, 1947-1948 (Box 407:5556)
    - Loom test--Wide drapers, 1947-1948 (Box 407:5557)
    - Miscellaneous, 1943-1947 (Box 407:5558)
    - Neps, 1943, 1947 (Box 407:5559)
    - Pickers--Cottn, 1947-1948 (Box 407:5560)
    - Pickers--R & W, undated (Box 407:5561)
    - Run outs, 1942-1947 (Box 407:5562)
    - Shipping department, 1948 March 23 (Box 407:5563)
    - Slasher tests, 1942-1948 (Box 407:5564)
    - Slubbers and Fine frames, undated (Box 407:5565)
    - Special Long draft spinning, 1948 September (Box 407:5566)
    - Spinning cotton--Filling, 1947-1948 (Box 407:5567)
    - Spinning cotton warp, 1946-1948 (Box 407:5568)
    - Spinning R & W Filling, 1948 (Box 407:5569)
    - Spinning R & W warp, 1947-1948 (Box 407:5570)
    - Spinning room, 1942-1948 (Box 407:5571)
    - Spinning speeds, 1942-1948 (Box 407:5572)
    - Twisters, 1946-1947 (Box 407:5573)
    - Weave room, 1942-1947 (Box 407:5574)
    - Weave room--Battery hands, 1948-1951 (Box 407:5575)
    - Weae room--Filling run test, 1948-1951 (Box 408:5576)
    - Weave shop--Battery test, 1946-1948 (Box 408:5577)
    - Weave shop--Filling run test, 1947 (Box 408:5578)
    - Winders, 1947-1948 (Box 408:5579)
    - Yarn size--Cotton filling, 1948 (Box 408:5580)
    - Yarn size--Cotton warp, 1947-1949 (Box 408:5581)
    - Yarn size--R & W filling, 1947-1948 (Box 408:5582)
    - Yarn size--R & W warp, 1947-1948 (Box 408:5583)
  - American Cotton Manufacturers Institute, Inc. compiled reports
    - 1955 (Box 408:5584)
    - 1956 (Box 408:5585)
  - Fabric sample books, undated (Box 408:5586)
  - Fabric sample book, undated (Box 409)
  - Fabric sample book, undated (Box 410)
  - Fabric sample book, undated (Box 411)
  - Fabric sample book, undated (Box 437)
- Series XIX: Labor Records, 1932-1942
  - Subseries A: Personnel and Payroll records, 1935-1942
    - Payroll analysis, 1938 November (Box 408:5587)
    - Payroll analysis, 1939 November 27 (Box 408:5588)
    - Payroll analysis, 1940 (Box 408:5589)
    - Payroll analysis, 1941 August 4 (Box 408:5590)
    - Payroll summary, 1939 November 27 (Box 408:5591)
    - Payroll summary, 1941 April 7 (Box 408:5592)
    - Payroll summary, 1941 August 4 (Box 408:5593)
    - Personnel file, 1935-1941 (Box 408:5594)
    - Wage survey, 1942 (Box 408:5595)
    - Standard weekly payroll budget, 1942 (Box 408:5596)
  - Subseries B: Labor Housing, 1932, 1941
    - Sale of Quinebaug housing, 1934 (Box 408:5597)
    - Sale of Quinebaug housing (printed material), 1934 (Box 408:5598)
    - Sale of Wauregan housing, 1941 (Box 408:5599)
    - Sale of Wauregan housing (printed material), 1941 (Box 408:5600)
- Series XX: Sales Records, 1935-1952
  - Account book, 1934-1936 (Box 408:5601)
  - Account book, 1937-1940 (Box 408:5602)
  - Yarn Orders, 1933-1934 (Box 408:5603)
  - Yarn Orders, 1935-1939 (Box 408:5604)
  - Yarn Orders, 1940-1941 (Box 408:5605)
  - Accepted bids, 1951-1952 (Box 408:5606)
- Series XXI: Photographs and prints, undated, 1795-1955
  - Photographic prints
    - Wauregan Mills
      - Exterior views
        - Ground level (Box 412:5607-5610)
        - Ground level--color slides, undated (Box 412:5611)
        - Aerial, undated (Box 412:5612-5613)
        - View from smoke stack, 1938 March (Box 412:5614)
        - Smoke stack construction, 1911 (Box 412:5615)
        - Smoke stack repairs, undated (Box 412:5616-5620)
        - Dam repairs, undated (Box 412:5621-5622)
        - Dam repairs, 1934 (Box 412:5623)
        - Dam repairs, 1947 (Box 412:5624)
        - Oversize, undated (Box 435)
        - Album, undated (Box 440)
      - Interior views
        - Baling fabric, undated (Box 412:5625)
        - Boilers, undated (Box 412:5626)
        - Cafeteria, undated (Box 412:5627)
        - Carding machines, undated (Box 412:5628)
        - Combing machines, undated (Box 412:5629)
        - Cotton bales, undated (Box 412:5630)
        - Drawing machines, undated (Box 412:5631)
        - Floor space (empty), undated (Box 412:5632)
        - Looms, undated (Box 412:5633)
        - Machinery, undated (Box 412:5634-5638)
        - Machinery, 1942 (Box 412:5639-5640)
        - Offices, undated (Box 412:5641)
        - Pumps, undated (Box 412:5642)
        - Quillers or Filling winders, undated (Box 412:5643)
        - Slashers, undated (Box 412:5644)
        - Slubbers, undated (Box 412:5645)
        - Spinning machines, undated (Box 412:5646-5647)
        - Warping and winding machines, undated (Box 412:5648)
      - Groups
        - Employees, undated (Box 413:5649-5650)
        - Employees [8 mounted images], undated (Box 418:5697)
      - Individuals
        - Unidentified, undated (Box 413:5651-5653)
        - Unidentified, undated (Box 418:5698-5699)
        - John W. Atwood, undated (Box 413:5654)
        - J. S. Atwood, 1876 August 29 (Box 413:5655)
        - "Uncle Walter's Billiard Room" and others, undated (Box 413:5656)
        - J.A. Atwood, Jr., 1912 (Box not specified)
    - Flood, 1955
      - High water (Box 413:5657-5660)
      - Damage--Exterior (Box 413:5661-5663)
      - Damage--Interior (Box 413:5664-5667)
      - Albums (Box 414-415)
    - "E" Awards, ca. 1942-1945 (Box 413:5668-5673)
    - Wauregan, Connecticut
      - Town, undated (Box 413:5674-5675)
      - Town (Winter), undated (Box 418:5701)
      - Interior [Wauregan Church?], undated (Box 413:5676)
      - Baseball teams, undated (Box 413:5677)
  - Quinebaug Company
    - Exterior views
      - Ground level, undated (Box 413:5678)
      - Aerial, undated (Box 416:5679-5680)
      - Plant, undated (Box 418:5700)
    - Interior views
      - Slasher office, undated (Box 416:5681)
    - Camp Adeawonda [postcards], undated (Box 416:5683-5688)
    - Milk Bar, undated (Box 416:5691)
    - Unidentified Mill (3), undated (Box 418:5702)
  - Negatives
    - Milk Bar [Glass plate], undated (Box 417:5689-5690)
    - Aerial, undated (Box 417:5692)
    - Dam repair, [1955?] (Box 417:5693-5696)
  - Engravings
    - Public Room at the 5th Ward Museum Hotel, 1864 (Box 416:5705)
    - Ponemah Mills, undated (Box 416:5706)
    - Lists of prints bought, 1937 (Box 416:5707)
    - Quinebaug Mills, undated (Box 418:5703)
    - Weaving and textile manufacturing, undated, 1795, 1802 (Box 418:5704)
- Series XXII: Personal Papers, 1843-1966
  - J. A. Atwood, 1859-1958
    - Business Records
      - Calculations, 1900-1932 (Box 419:5708)
      - Lockwood Company, 1883-1910 (Box 419:5709)
      - Lockwood Company--Inventory, 1905 January (Box 419:5710)
      - Lockwood Company--Wage list, 1906-1910 (Box 419:5711)
      - Lockwood Company--Permission to transport cotton, 1867-1868 (Box 419:5712)
      - Williamsville Manufacturing Company, 1859-1902 (Box 419:5713)
      - Ponemah Mills, 1873-1932 (Box 419:5714)
      - Ponemah Mills blueprints, undated (Box OS:)
      - Quidnick-Windham Manufacturing Company--Development of water power, 1916, 1918 (Box 419:5715)
      - Lawton Mills, 1921, 1929 (Box 419:5716)
      - Lorraine Manufacturing Company, 1932 (Box 419:5717)
      - Nottingham Mill, 1899 (Box 419:5718)
      - Textile reports and clippings, 1921, 1931 (Box 419:5719)
      - American Mutual Liability Insurance Company--Board of Directors, 1944, 1947 (Box 419:5720)
      - American Mutual Liability Insurance Company--Financial Committee and published materials, 1919, 1937, 1944 (Box 419:5721)
      - Fireman's Mutual Insurance Company--Financial reports, 1944-1947 (Box 419:5722)
      - Union Mutual Fire Insurance Company--Charter and Financial reports, 1927-1928, 1944-1947 (Box 419:5723)
      - Insurance publications, 1930, 1944 (Box 419:5724)
      - Kennebec Water Power Company, 1909, 1910 (Box 419:5725)
      - Quinebaug River Public Warehouse, 1951-1958 (Box 419:5726)
      - Financial institutions--Company resolutions, 1922-1932 (Box 419:5727)
      - Published materials, 1922- 1924 (Box 419:5728-5729)
    - Personal Papers
      - Correspondence, 1890 (Box 419:5730)
      - Correspondence, 1889 (Box 419:5731)
      - Correspondence, 1915, 1916, 1919 (Box 419:5732)
      - Correspondence, 1920s (Box 419:5733)
      - Correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 419:5734)
      - Correspondence, 1930s (Box 419:5735)
      - Correspondence [from Miss Belcher], 1945-1946 (Box 419:5736)
      - Bill and receipts, 1875-1920 (Box 419:5737)
      - Check books, 1931-1932 (Box 419:5738)
      - Deeds, 1888-1918 (Box 419:5739)
      - Land records--Oak Bluffs, Massachusetts, 1923-1924 (Box 419:5740)
      - Personal papers, 1936, 1938-1943, 1949 (Box 419:5741)
  - Business Records, 1843-1966
    - A. D. Lockwood and Company--Journal [extensive water damage], 1843-1855 (Box 420)
    - Wauregan Library Association, 1866-1895 (Box 421)
    - Wauregan Water Company--Rent and water charges, 1949-1966 (Box 422)
  - Estate Records, 1886-1934
    - J. S. Atwood--Receipted bills, 1886 (Box 423:5742)
    - J. S. Atwood--Receipted bills, 1887 (Box 423:5743)
    - John W. Atwood--Receipts, 1923-1926 (Box 423:5744)
    - John W. Atwood--Receipts, 1927-1931 (Box 423:5745)
    - John W. Atwood--Rhode Island Hospital Trust statements, 1924-1929 (Box 423:5746)
    - John W. Atwood--Rhode Island Hospital Trust statements, 1930-1934 (Box 423:5747)
    - John W. Atwood--Rhode Island Hospital Trust cancelled checks, 1925-1929 (Box 423:5748)
    - John W. Atwood--Rhode Island Hospital Trust cancelled checks, 1930-1934 (Box 423:5749)
    - John W. Atwood--Rhode Island Hospital Trust checkbook and account book, 1918-1925 (Box 423:5750)
    - John W. Atwood--The Thames National Bank statements, 1924-1925 (Box 423:5751)
    - John W. Atwood--The Thames National Bank cacelled checks, 1924-1925 (Box 423:5752)
    - John W. Atwood records, 1923-1925 (Box 423:5753)
    - John W. Atwood records, 1925-1933 (Box 423:5754)
    - John W. Atwood records, 1923-1925 (Box 423:5755)
    - John W. Atwood records, 1924-1925 (Box 423:5756)
    - Julia A. M. Atwood--Income tax records, 1913-1925 (Box 423:5757)
    - Julia A. M. Atwood--Division of Estate, 1924 (Box 423:5758)
    - Julia A. M. Atwood records, 1919-1924 (Box 423:5759-5760)
    - Arnold Fenner--Income tax records, 1913-1924 (Box 423:5761)
    - Bucklin Mathewson--Income tax records, 1917 (Box 423:5762)
    - Helen M. Sampson--Income tax records, 1922-1923 (Box 423:5763)
    - Helen M. Sampson--Legal and financial records, 1901-1933 (Box 423:5764)
  - Legal Records, 1847-1934
    - Appointment of Executor, 1869-1934 (Box 423:5765)
    - Appointment of Guardian, 1927-1930 (Box 423:5766)
    - Power of Attorney, 1882, 1931 (Box 423:5767)
    - Assignment of Trust, 1875, 1876, 1890, 1920 (Box 423:5768)
    - Bankruptcy, 1905 (Box 423:5769)
    - Deeds, 1877, 1901 (Box 423:5770)
    - Court documents, 1847, 1909, 1924 (Box 423:5771)
    - Wills, 1881-1925 (Box 423:5772-5773)
  - J. A. Atwood, Jr., undated, 1912-1922
    - Correspondence, 1916-1919 (Box 424:5774)
    - Correspondence, 1920-1922 (Box 424:5775)
    - Correspondence: Vegi-Feeds, Inc., 1918-1921 (Box 424:5776)
    - Bills and receipts, 1916 August - December (Box 424:5777)
    - Bills and receipts, 1917 (Box 424:5778)
    - Bills and receipts, 1918 January - June (Box 424:5779)
    - Bills and receipts, 1918 July - December (Box 424:5780)
    - Bills and receipts, 1919 January - June (Box 424:5781)
    - Bills and receipts, 1919 July - December (Box 424:5782)
    - Bills and receipts, 1920 January - May (Box 424:5783)
    - Bills and receipts, 1920 June - December (Box 424:5784)
    - Bills and receipts, 1921 (Box 424:5785)
    - Financial records, 1918-1920 (Box 424:5786)
    - Land records, undated, 1918 (Box 424:5787)
    - The Burton Range Company--Assets and liabilities, 1919-1920 (Box 424:5788)
    - Personal papers, 1920 (Box 424:5789)
  - J. A. Atwood, III, undated, 1913-1957
    - "Coming of the Machine Age" and "Wauregan Mills", undated (Box 424:5894)
    - Correspondence, 1953, 1956-1957 (Box 424:5790)
    - Town of Plainfield, Board of Education, 1954-1955 (Box 424:5791-5793)
    - Town of Plainfield, Board of Education, 1955-1956 (Box 424:5794)
  - J. S. Atwood, 1864-1885
    - Correspondence, 1868-1869, 1885 (Box 424:5795)
    - Financial records, 1880-1885 (Box 424:5796)
    - Deeds and Patent license, 1864, 1868, 1880 (Box 424:5797)
    - Bills and receipts (Mrs. Atwood), 1884-1885 (Box 424:5798)
  - J. W. Atwood, 1885-1925
    - Correspondence, 1888-1922 (Box 424:5799)
    - Financial records, 1885-1925 (Box 424:5800)
  - Julia A. M. Atwood, 1885-1903
    - Legal and financial records, 1885, 1889, 1903 (Box 424:5801)
  - Frances van Hall, 1954-1957
    - Compositions, 1954-1957 (Box 424:5802)
  - Other People, 1854- circa 1930
    - Correspondence, legal and financial records, 1854-1931 (Box 424:5803)
    - Raymond Kienholz Travel diaries, 1928 (Box 424:5804)
- Series XXIII: Architectural Drawings and Blueprints, undated, 1866, 1876, 1895, 1918, 1931
  - unspecified (Box OS:5881)
    - Bird's Eye View of Quinebaug Mill and copy, undated
    - Architectural plans and drawings (20, 21, 23, 30, 35-37), undated
    - Mechanical drawings, map, blueprints (7, 23-25, 27, 38, 46-47), undated
  - unspecified (Box OS:5882)
    - Mechanical drawings (16, 97, 26, 31, 34), undated
    - Blueprints and floor plans Boarding House to apartments (98), undated
  - unspecified (Box OS:5883)
    - Layout of Quinebaug mills, undated
    - Map of Wauregan physical plant, undated
    - Oversize materials, undated
  - unspecified (Box OS:5884)
    - Blueprints, plans, details of power systems (80, 93, 87-90, 96), undated
  - unspecified (Box OS:5885)
    - Blueprints, plans, details and changes (14, 86, 73-79, 72, 12, 121), undated
  - unspecified (Box OS:5886)
    - Blueprints and plans for condensers, boilers, piping, sprinklers and plat (94-95, 81-85, 91-92, 70-71), undated
  - unspecified (Box OS:5887)
    - Layout of physical plant Wauregan and Quinebaug (5), undated
  - Buildings/Structures/Property Plans/Blueprints (Box OS:5888)
    - Relocation Route 12, undated
    - NYNH&H RR Station, side track service, undated
    - Mills (Fountain Street/Shepard Hill Road/Grove Street), 1895
    - Plat (Brooklyn, CT), 1918
    - U.S. Rayon Company property plat, undated
    - Danielson and Norwich Street Railway, undated
    - Wheelhouse, undated
    - Power Plant, undated
    - Economizer, undated
  - Building/Structures Plans/Blueprints (Box OS:5889)
    - Chimney, undated
    - Wasteway, undated
    - Turbine and Engine rooms, undated
    - Power plant, undated
    - Heine boiler, undated
    - Wheelhouse, undated
    - Looms, undated
    - Power wiring, undated
    - Economizer house, undated
  - Machinery Plans/Blueprints (Box OS:5890)
    - NYNH&H RR Station, undated
    - Pans & Tightener pulley, undated
    - Transisor application, undated
    - Switchboard, undated
    - Corliss Engine, undated
    - Belt tightener, undated
    - Boiler feed pressure pump, undated
    - Hercules turbines, undated
    - Hercules wheels, undated
    - Shafting arrangements, undated
    - Engine Foundation, undated
    - New Turbine installation, undated
  - Building/Structures Plans/Blueprints (Box OS:5891)
    - Wasteway, undated
    - Chimney, undated
    - Turbine Condensor, undated
    - Wheelhouse, undated
    - Suction Well, undated
    - Engine Foundation, undated
    - Standpipe, undated
    - Pump, undated
    - Piping for waterworks, undated
    - Pumping Station, undated
    - Washer, undated
  - unspecified (Box OS:5892)
    - Plat of Nashawaug Water-Power Estate, 1866
    - Corner of Water and Franklin Streets, undated
    - Plat of Fountain Street/Shepard Hill Road/Grove Street, undated
    - MS sketch of property (3), undated
    - Wauregan Dam, 1876
  - unspecified (Box OS:5893)
    - Scale drawing of Front office, purchasing, personnel, undated
    - Griswold Mills, undated
    - Specifications for Walling-in, undated
    - Economizer Equipment drawings, undated
    - Ponemah Mills, 1931
- Series XXIV: Memorabilia, undated, 1934, 1945
  - Mailbag, undated (Box 438)
  - Wauregan Fire Alarm sign (wood), undated (Box 438)
  - Treasurer's office sign (brass), undated (Box 439)
  - NRA Blue Eagle poster, 1934 (Box 439)
  - Cigarette sales permit, 1945 (Box 439)